(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
マスクの着用にご協力ください / 公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please wear a mask and refrain from cheering out loud.
公演中は席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from moving from your seat during the performance.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします
Please set your mobile phone to silent mode.
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio recording, and filming are prohibited.
#わためソロライブ
#WatameSoloLive
SNSでの感想投稿OK / スクリーンショット投稿OK
Posting impressions and screenshots on SNS is OK.
動画の切り抜き・ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止します
Clipping, mirror streaming, and illegal uploading are strictly prohibited.
フラワースタンド紹介
Flower Stand Introduction
単品販売グッズ
Merchandise for Individual Sale
マスクの着用にご協力ください / 公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please wear a mask and refrain from cheering out loud.
公演中は席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from moving from your seat during the performance.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします
Please set your mobile phone to silent mode.
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio recording, and filming are prohibited.
#わためソロライブ
#WatameSoloLive
SNSでの感想投稿OK / スクリーンショット投稿OK
Posting impressions and screenshots on SNS is OK.
動画の切り抜き・ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止します
Clipping, mirror streaming, and illegal uploading are strictly prohibited.
マスクの着用にご協力ください / 公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please wear a mask and refrain from cheering out loud.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします
Please set your mobile phone to silent mode.
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio recording, and filming are prohibited.
Attention ご来場の皆さんへ
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Attention: To all attendees
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
公演中は席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from vocal cheering and from
moving between seats during the performance.
COCOAを使用していただけるため、携帯電話の
電源はお切りにならずマナーモードの設定を…
To allow the use of the COCOA app, please do
not turn off your phone; use silent mode...
…お願いします。撮影・録音・録画は
禁止とさせていただきます。
...instead. Photography, audio recording,
and filming are strictly prohibited.
HASHTAG #わためソロライブ
SNSへの感想・スクショ投稿OK！
HASHTAG #WatameSoloLive
Posting impressions and screenshots to SNS is OK!
録音・録画・ミラー配信は禁止です。
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Recording and mirror streaming are prohibited.
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Flower Stands
フラワースタンド紹介
Flower Stand Introduction
単品販売グッズ 1
Individual Merchandise for Sale 1
単品販売グッズ 2
Individual Merchandise for Sale 2
単品販売グッズ 3
Individual Merchandise for Sale 3
Attention ご来場の皆さんへ
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Attention: To all attendees
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
公演中は席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from vocal cheering and from
moving between seats during the performance.
COCOAを使用していただけるため、携帯電話の
電源はお切りにならずマナーモードの設定を…
To allow the use of the COCOA app, please do
not turn off your phone; use silent mode...
…お願いします。撮影・録音・録画は
禁止とさせていただきます。
...instead. Photography, audio recording,
and filming are strictly prohibited.
HASHTAG #わためソロライブ
SNSへの感想・スクショ投稿OK！
HASHTAG #WatameSoloLive
Posting impressions and screenshots to SNS is OK!
録音・録画・ミラー配信は禁止です。
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Recording and mirror streaming are prohibited.
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Flower Stands
フラワースタンド紹介
Flower Stand Introduction
単品販売グッズ 1
Individual Merchandise for Sale 1
単品販売グッズ 2
Individual Merchandise for Sale 2
単品販売グッズ 3
Individual Merchandise for Sale 3
Individual Sale Goods 3
マスクの着用、発声禁止、座席移動禁止へのご協力をお願いします。
Please wear a mask, refrain from cheering, and stay in your seat.
COCOA利用のためマナーモード設定をお願いします。撮影・録音は禁止です。
Set phones to silent mode for COCOA. Recording and photography are prohibited.
SNS・スクショ投稿OK。録音・録画・ミラー配信は厳禁です。
SNS posts and screenshots are OK. Recording and mirror streaming are strictly prohibited.
Flower Stands フラワースタンド紹介
Flower Stands - Introduction
単品販売グッズ 1
Individual Sale Goods 1
単品販売グッズ 2
Individual Sale Goods 2
単品販売グッズ 3
Individual Sale Goods 3
マスクの着用、発声禁止、座席移動禁止へのご協力をお願いします。
Please wear a mask, refrain from cheering, and stay in your seat.
COCOA利用のためマナーモード設定をお願いします。撮影・録音は禁止です。
Set phones to silent mode for COCOA. Recording and photography are prohibited.
SNS・スクショ投稿OK。録音・録画・ミラー配信は厳禁です。
SNS posts and screenshots are OK. Recording and mirror streaming are strictly prohibited.
Flower Stands フラワースタンド紹介
Flower Stands - Introduction
単品販売グッズ 1
Individual Sale Goods 1
単品販売グッズ 2
Individual Sale Goods 2
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがヴァイスシュヴァルツに参戦！
Hololive Production joins Weiss Schwarz!
トライアルデッキ＋ ホロライブプロダクション、
Trial Deck+ Hololive Production,
好評発売中！
now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
D4DJ Groovy Mix!
ホロライブ 楽曲コラボ開催中だよ！
The Hololive song collaboration is underway!
ドドーンと、いろんな楽曲を実装しちゃうんだって！
A whole lot of songs are being added!
ゲームBGMやインスト、カバー楽曲も、
Play game BGMs, instrumentals, and cover songs,
DJ気分で遊べちゃう！
all while feeling like a DJ!
繋がろう、グルミクで！
Let's connect in Groovy Mix!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも、
With the Hololive Production booster packs,
止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz is unstoppable!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション、好評発売中！
Booster Pack Hololive Production, now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
本日は
Today,
角巻わため 1st Live 「わためぇ Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo」 Supported by ブシロードにご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
thank you very much for coming to Tsunomaki Watame's 1st Live, "Watame Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo" Supported by Bushiroad.
記念すべき角巻わためのファーストソロライブを楽しみにしてくださっている、わためいとの皆さん。
To all the Watamates who have been looking forward to Tsunomaki Watame's memorable first solo live.
本日は、どうぞよろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you for being here today!
イェーイ！
Yay!
さて、公演を最後まで楽しんでいただくために、皆様へいくつかご案内をさせてください。
Now, I have a few announcements to make to ensure everyone can enjoy the performance until the end.
まず初めに、会場のわためいとの皆様へのご案内です。
First, some announcements for the Watamates here at the venue.
ロビー、客席内では、マスクの着用が必須となります。
Masks must be worn in the lobby and the seating area.
公演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点から、ご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from shouting or vocal cheering during the performance to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
ぜひ、さっきみたいな拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いします。
Instead, please support me with applause and penlights, like you just did.
また、会場内では立って応援していただいても問題ございませんが、周りのお客様にご迷惑にならないようご配慮お願いいたします。
Also, standing up to cheer is permitted, but please be considerate of those around you.
会場内では、スタッフの方の指示に従ってください。
Please follow the instructions of the staff within the venue.
客席内で、周りのお客様に迷惑をかけるような危険行為はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from any dangerous behavior in the seating area that may disturb others.
会場内では、携帯電話、スマートフォンをマナーモードにしていただきますよう、お願いいたします。
Please make sure your mobile phones and smartphones are set to silent mode.
本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入るため...
Since cameras for video streaming and photography will be inside the venue for this performance...
...客席のお客様の様子が、わためいとみんなの様子が...
...the audience in the seating area, all you Watamates...
...映り込む場合がございます。
...may appear in the footage.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションや今後の活動に使用する可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotion and future activities.
いいよね？
That's okay, right?
お、いいよね！
Oh, it's okay!
いってことだよね！ありがとう！
I'll take that as a yes! Thank you!
公演中、ライブの様子を撮影することは、演出の都合上、禁止とさせていただきます。
Due to production reasons, photography and recording of the performance are prohibited.
ペンライトは、周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮お願いいたします。
Please be careful with your penlights so as not to disturb those around you.
頭の上に出したり、大きく左右に振り回されますと、後ろのお客様や周りのお客様のご迷惑となる場合がございます。
Holding them above your head or swinging them wildly may disturb the people behind or around you.
スタッフさんが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご了承ください。
Please note that staff members may give you a warning.
以上のことが守られない場合...
If these rules are not followed...
...いないと思うんだけど、安全確保のため公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただくこともございます。
...which I don't think will happen, the performance may be paused or even cancelled for safety reasons.
最後に、ご気分のすぐれない場合など何かございましたら、お早めに、お近くのスタッフにお申し付けください。
Lastly, if you start feeling unwell or have any other issues, please inform a nearby staff member as soon as possible.
また、地震などの緊急時には、スタッフが誘導いたします。
In case of an emergency such as an earthquake, the staff will guide you.
スタッフの指示があるまで、おきゃ...ま...ま...
Until you receive instructions from the staff, pleas— wait—
間違えたね！
I messed up!
応援ありがとう！
Thanks for the support!
お席にてお待ちください。
Please wait in your seat.
続いて、配信でご覧のわためいとの皆さんへの注意事項をお伝えします。
Next, here are some reminders for the Watamates watching the stream.
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは、固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirror streaming, and illegal uploads of this live performance are strictly prohibited.
スクリーンショットを撮影して、画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です！ぜひお願いします！
Taking screenshots and posting them on social media is more than welcome! Please do!
本公演のハッシュタグは、「#わためソロライブ」です。
The hashtag for this performance is "#わためソロライブ".
ぜひハッシュタグを使って、ライブを一緒に盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag and let's get hyped for the live show together!
また、ライブ配信について、データの通信量が多くなることが想定されるため...
Also, as high data usage is expected for the live stream...
...スマートフォンでご覧になる場合には、Wi-Fiでのご利用を推奨いたします。
...we recommend using a Wi-Fi connection if you are watching on a smartphone.
インターネット回線の接続が不安定な場合は...
If your internet connection is unstable...
...クッソザコ回線...
...a "total trash connection"...
...の場合は、配信動画のクオリティを保証できません。
...we cannot guarantee the quality of the stream.
最善の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、生配信の特性上...
We will do our best to prepare for the live stream, but due to the nature of live broadcasting...
...特性上、不慮の障害で、映像の乱れや一時停止等が起こる可能性があります。あらかじめご了承ください。
...there is a possibility of technical glitches, such as video distortion or pauses. We appreciate your understanding.
さて、わためからのご案内は... あ、私からのご案内は、以上となります。
Well, that's all the announcements from Watame... I mean, from me.
開演まであと少し。私はステージに出る準備をしてきます！
Only a little longer until the show starts. I'm going to get ready for the stage!
それでは、開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
So then, please wait a little longer until the show starts.
単品販売グッズ ①
ライブTシャツ：¥4,000 / タオル：¥2,500
Single Item Sales Goods 1
Live T-shirt: ¥4,000 / Towel: ¥2,500
単品販売グッズ ②
ペンライト：¥3,500 / わためのおもしろパリピサングラス：¥3,000
Single Item Sales Goods 2
Penlight: ¥3,500 / Watame's Funny Party People Sunglasses: ¥3,000
単品販売グッズ ③
キービジュアルB2タペストリー：¥3,000
わためいとアイマスク：¥2,000 / セトリキーホルダー：¥1,500
Single Item Sales Goods 3
Key Visual B2 Tapestry: ¥3,000
Watamate Eye Mask: ¥2,000 / Setlist Key Holder: ¥1,500
Attention
マスクの着用にご協力ください
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
公演中は席の移動はお控えください
Attention
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
Please refrain from cheering out loud during the performance.
Please refrain from moving seats during the performance.
Attention
COCOAを使用していただくため携帯電話の電源はお切りにならずマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします。
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます。
Attention
Please do not turn off your phone and set it to silent mode for COCOA.
Photography, audio recording, and filming are prohibited.
Information
SNSでの感想投稿OK / スクリーンショット投稿OK
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします。
Information
Posting impressions on SNS is OK / Posting screenshots is OK
Recording, filming, mirror distribution, and illegal uploading are strictly prohibited.
本日は角巻わため 1st Live わためぇ Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo
Thank you very much for joining us today for Tsunomaki Watame's 1st Live: Watame Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo,
supported by Bushiroad にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
supported by Bushiroad.
大変長らくお待たせしました。本公演は間もなく開演いたします。
Thank you very much for waiting. The performance will begin shortly.
会場の皆さんも、配信でご覧の皆さんも、一緒に盛り上がる準備はできていますか？
To everyone here at the venue and everyone watching the livestream, are you ready to get excited together?
いいですね！最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
That's the spirit! Let's have fun together until the very end!
わためぇ Night Fever!! スタート！
Watame Night Fever!! Start!
おはようのうた
The Morning Song
おはようのうた 今日が始まる
The morning song, today begins.
みんな、いくよ！
Everyone, here we go!
どんな一日を描こうかな
I wonder what kind of day I should draw.
ワクワクお絵かき 夢物語綴ろう
Excitingly drawing, let's write a dream story.
そんな子供じゃいられないよ
I can't stay a child like that.
分かったフリした大人の自分が言う
Says the adult version of me who pretends to understand.
笑いながら 苦いこと話したリ
Talking about bitter things while laughing.
泣きながら ゲームをしてたり
Playing games while crying.
思いもかけないことのその全部が 君のせい 本当にありがとう
All those unexpected things are because of you, thank you so much.
「おはよう」って「おはよう」って 今日もまた言えるね
Saying "Good morning," "Good morning," we can say it again today.
君と重ねた色がふえ
The colors I've layered with you increase.
難しいことは分からない 無邪気な笑顔に助かる
I don't understand difficult things, I'm saved by an innocent smile.
何度でも君を呼び送るよ
I'll call out to you again and again.
せーので駆け出したあの日から 随分遠くへ
Since that day we dashed off on "Ready, go!", we've come quite far.
やっとここまで来たけれど
Finally, we've come this far, but...
ねぇ、今 君が見てる私は どんな顔して
Hey, what kind of face do I have now as you're looking at me?
ちゃんと笑えているのかな
I wonder if I'm smiling properly.
誰も知らない頑張りがあったね
There was hard work that no one knew about.
君も私もそうだから 何度も言う「ありがとう」
Because it's like that for both you and me, I'll say "Thank you" many times.
「おかえり」って「ただいま」って 今日もまだ言えるよ
Saying "Welcome home," "I'm back," we can still say it today.
君と重ねた色がふえ
The colors I've layered with you increase.
白くて柔らかい夜に 泣きだす声は震えても
In the white and soft night, even if the voice that starts to cry trembles,
何度でも朝を迎えた
Morning has come again and again.
おはよう また眠り
Good morning, back to sleep
いってらっしゃい 行ってきます
Have a safe trip, I'm off
ただいま おかえり
I'm home, welcome back
おやすみなさい
Good night
いってらっしゃい 行ってきます
Have a safe trip, I'm off
ちゃんとまた会えるよ 君と
I'll definitely see you again, with you
見つけたここが好き
I love it here that I found
新しい朝を恐れない
Not afraid of the new morning
無邪気な笑顔に助かる
Saved by your innocent smile
また帰る場所があるから
Because I have a place to return to
何度でも君を見送るよ
I'll see you off any number of times
愛昧ショコラーテ
Ai-mai Chocolate
わためぇ Night Fever!! In Zepp Tokyo!
Watame Night Fever!! In Zepp Tokyo!
サイリウムたくさん振ってくれ！ せーの！
Wave your penlights a lot! Ready, go!
あー混ぜちゃった
Ah, I mixed it in
隠してたわけじゃないの
It's not that I was hiding it
きっとただ言ってないだけ
I just probably didn't say it
だって恥ずかしいんだもん
It's just that I'm shy
意外と寂しん坊
Surprisingly lonely
意外と甘えん坊
Surprisingly spoiled
意外と慌てん坊
Surprisingly flustered
意外と照れ屋
Surprisingly shy
丸い飛行機雲
Round contrails
飛び出したカップケーキ
Jumping cupcakes
3回目コンディショナー
Third time conditioner
甘すぎパズル
Too sweet puzzle
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢見心地
Fluffy, floating dreamlike feeling
ひとつひとつ数えて おやすみなさい
Counting them one by one, good night
密かに芽生えた この気持ち
This feeling that sprouted secretly
まっすぐ見つめないで
Don't look straight at me
何だっけ？
What was it?
言葉にしちゃときっとそうじゃない
When I put it into words, it's probably not that
照れちゃうだけ おちゃらけちゃうじゃない
I'm just shy, I'm just joking around
本当の本当は隠したいんじゃないの
Actually, I don't really want to hide it
もうそうじゃないのにな
It's not like that anymore though
曖昧なんじゃない
It's not ambiguous
この気持ちは間違いじゃない
This feeling is not a mistake
指切りげんまん
Pinky promise
かなり閉じこもって
Even if I'm quite shut-in
優柔不断でも
And indecisive
絶対に毎日
Every single day
会いに来てくれるよね？
You'll come to see me, right?
本来臆病で
Inherently cowardly
案外気難しい
And unexpectedly difficult
全然変わらずに
Not changing at all
元来君ばっか
Originally just you
当たり前のようにキュンとしちゃう
I naturally get heart-throbs
キミがいないとガッカリしちゃう
If you're not here, I get disappointed
本当の本当にションボリしちゃうわ
I really, really get downcast
会いたくなっちゃうな
I start wanting to see you
後悔ばっかしちゃう
I'll just regret it
この心も勇気出しちゃえ
Let this heart also take courage
この指とまれ
Join in
みんな！ 見て見て見て！
Everyone! Look, look, look!
こんなおっきいステージで歌えて嬉しい！
I'm happy to be able to sing on such a big stage!
どんどん！ 楽しい！
Dondon! It's fun!
最高の1日にするから！
I'll make it the best day!
最後まで一緒にいてな！
Stay with me until the end!
弱いところ気づかれたり...
Having my weak spots noticed...
寂しさごと包まれたり
Wrapped up with loneliness
いつまでも笑い合ったり
Laughing with each other forever
たまにはムッと喧嘩をしたり
Sometimes getting huffy and having a fight
ずっとずっとそばにいてほしい
I want you to be by my side forever and ever
約束だぞっ
Promise me!
いっちゃった///
I said it!
もしかしたら運命かも
Maybe it's fate
赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
Maybe I can see the red thread of fate
本当はほらバレてるのかも
Actually, hey, maybe it's been found out
目が合わせらんないかも
Maybe I can't look you in the eye
曖昧なんてない
There's no ambiguity
たくさん私を見てて
Look at me a lot
指切りった！
Pinky promised!
メイデイ、メイデイ
Mayday, mayday
メイデイ、声は届いてる？
Mayday, is my voice reaching you?
心がチクッと痛い痛い
My heart feels a sharp pain
ベイビー、なんて魅惑的
Baby, how enchanting
見せつけていくの まっすぐにクラクラ
I'll keep showing it off, straight to a daze
メイデイ、それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's not enough
すぐにもっともっと夢中スカイ
Soon, more and more, into a trance sky
ヘイ、ヘイ、もっとじらしてよ
Hey hey, tease me more
あなたの心に入ってたいの
I want to enter your heart
あー、見え透いた甘い罠
Ah, a transparently sweet trap
あー、ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I fall for it?
あー、自在にコントロールして
Ah, control me as you wish
いたい、はずなのに
I want to be, even though I shouldn't be...
クラクラと酔っちゃいそうな舞に誘われ
Invited to a dance that makes me feel dizzy and drunk
クラクラと酔ってちゃいそうな夢へ
To a dream that makes me feel dizzy and drunk
もうメイデイ、逃がさない
Now Mayday, I won't let you get away
負けだせ クラクラ
It's a loss, they say, dizzy
言っちゃうのはなんでも君のせい
Everything I say is all your fault
絶体絶命にして
Put me in a desperate situation
メイデイ、舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't take the helm
気持ちがもやっと晴れないし
My feelings are hazy and won't clear
ベイビー、なんか居られない
Baby, I can't stay like this
いまドキドキが one more, one more, one more, one more
Now my heart is racing, one more, one more, one more, one more
絶対あるわけないじゃない
There's no way it's real, right?
絶対にただの勘違い
It's absolutely just a misunderstanding
そんな手のひらの上で
In the palm of your hand like that
躍らされているこの感じ
This feeling of being danced around
だってもう透け出すような愛を
Because, a love that's already starting to show through...
耳触りなんか変、私じゃないや
The way it feels on my ears is strange, it's not me
もうメイデイ、嫌々、でも惚れちゃいそうな私を
Now Mayday, no, no, but me, who's about to fall in love...
困らせてなんか私 狂わせて
Trouble me, drive me crazy,
絶体絶命にして
put me in a desperate situation
ねえ、どうして
Hey, why is it...
愛はいたずらするんだろう
That love plays tricks on us?
ねえ、いつかは
Hey, will...
この痛みも消えるの？
this pain also disappear someday?
本来は案外簡単に
Originally, it's quite easily
否定して壊れちゃうけど
denied and broken, but...
着飾るよ 心を
I'll dress up my heart
気がつけば手を伸ばしちゃって
Before I knew it, I was reaching out my hand
その尊さ クラクラしちゃう
That preciousness makes me dizzy
君も手を伸ばしてくれ、ほら
You too, reach out your hand, look
いたい、ここにいたいほどに
I want to be here, so much that I want to stay
落ち着く場所、その手で触れてよ
Touch the place where I feel at peace with your hands
ほらメイデイ
Look, Mayday
クラクラと酔っちゃいそうな舞に誘われ
Invited to a dance that makes me feel dizzy and drunk
クラクラと酔ってちゃいそうな夢へ
To a dream that makes me feel dizzy and drunk
もうメイデイ、help me, rescue me, save me, mayday
Now Mayday, help me, rescue me, save me, Mayday
タイムを君は　掻き回せさ
Keep stirring up the time.
溢れ出したんだ
It's started to overflow.
もう目覚めて
Now, wake up.
あー、こんばんどどどー！
Ah, Konban-dododo!
ちょっと水飲んでもいいかな？
Can I drink some water?
いいかな？
Is it okay?
みんな、こんばんどう、ぞ... あはは
Everyone, welcome... haha
ちょっと水飲みますね。
I'm going to drink some water now.
あー、水うめーなー。
Ah, water tastes so good.
謎な拍手。あははは。
Mysterious applause. Hahaha.
水って、うめぇね！イエーイ！
Water is delicious! Yay!
水って、うめぇよなー！
Water really is the best!
あはは、なんだろうね。えー、
Hahaha, what was that? Uhm,
角巻わため 1st Live
Tsunomaki Watame 1st Live:
わためぇ Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo
Watame Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo
いよいよ始まったぞー！
It's finally started!
みんな、見に来てくれて本当にありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you all so much for coming! Thank you!
ついにわため初の単独ソロライブ。
Finally, Watame's first-ever solo live concert.
みんな、楽しみにしてたよなー！なー！
You've all been looking forward to this, right? Right?
なー！
Right?!
配信見てくれてる人も楽しみにしてたよねー。
I'm sure everyone watching the stream was excited too.
今日はね、ハッシュタグ「#わためソロライブ」でね、
Today, I'd like you to use the hashtag "#わためソロライブ"
たくさんたくさん呟いてほしいんだよなー。いいかな？
and tweet about the show as much as you can. Is that okay?
でも見るのに夢中か、みんな。ねー。
But maybe you're all too focused on watching? Heh.
わための魅力にやられてるんじゃないのー？
Maybe you're being captivated by Watame's charm?
やめとこうか調子乗るの、あれ、やめとこうね、あはは。
Better stop getting ahead of myself. Let's stop that, haha.
あ、おっ、調子に乗ってもいいってことなのかなー？
Ah, oh, so it's okay to get a bit cocky?
変な動きやめとこうね。せっかくのソロライブなのにね。
I'll stop these weird moves. Even though it's a special solo live.
「#わためソロライブ」でね、今日たくさんたくさん呟いてほしいなと思います！
I'd love for you to tweet a whole lot using "#わためソロライブ" today!
では、現地にせっかく来てくれてるみんなともね、遊びたいと思うんですけど、
Now, I'd like to have some fun with everyone here at the venue,
ペンライト持ってますかー？
do you have your penlights ready?
おっ、それ何色？ みんなそれ黄色だね！すごい！
Oh, what color is that? Everyone's got yellow! Amazing!
わためカラーだね！ペンライト振って振って振って！
It's Watame color! Wave those penlights! Wave them, wave them!
見えてるよー！あ、うちわ持ってくれてる人もありがとうねー！見えてるよー！
I see you! And thanks to those holding fans too! I see you!
せっかくだから見ちゃおうかなー。
Since I'm here, let me take a good look.
あ、見えてるよー！最前の人たち首痛くない？
Ah, I see you! People in the front row, aren't your necks hurting?
わためもね、あ、大丈夫？
Watame also... Ah, you're okay?
わためもね、あの、みんなのお席の方に行ってね、
Watame actually went to check out the seating area
リハの時に見たりしたんだけどね、ちょっと前の方首痛いよね。
during rehearsal, and the front row does strain the neck a bit.
なんかさ、あの、イケメンのポーズみたいになっちゃうよね。
It's like you're all stuck in a 'cool guy' pose.
声出せないの辛いね。受けてるのかわかんないよ。
It's tough not being able to cheer out loud. I can't tell if it's landing.
滑ってないかな？大丈夫かな？
Am I flopping? Is everything okay?
受けてる受けてる、あはは。
You are enjoying it, hahaha.
こういう時に拍手してもらえるとね、安心するので助かるよ。みんなありがとう。
Hearing you applaud at times like this puts me at ease. Thanks, everyone.
あとは... あとはちょっとステップとかはダメみたいなんだけどさ、
Also... it seems dancing along with steps is a no-go,
あの、上半身なら動かしてもいいらしいからさ、
but I heard it's okay to move your upper body,
上半身でわためへの愛を伝えてもらってもいいかな？恥ずかしい？
so could you show your love for Watame with your upper body? Are you shy?
何かこう、手とかさ。あ、やってくれてる！
Maybe move your hands? Oh, you're doing it!
あ、いいいね！フニフニダンス、いいいね！あ、いいねー！
Ah, nice! The Funifuni dance, nice! Ah, nice!
さすがわためぇ Night Fever!! 毎週踊ってるだけあるね！
As expected of Watame Night Fever!! It shows you've been dancing every week!
いや、これやってほしかったんだ、ありがとうね。
Yeah, I really wanted to see this, thanks!
配信民は寂しんじゃねーの？
Aren't the stream viewers feeling left out?
コメント見えてますよー。
I see your comments!
でもね、ちょっとラグがあってね、
There's a bit of a lag, but it's fine.
大丈夫、でも大丈夫、みんなが...
It's fine because I'll...
何言ってくれるかちょっと予言しながら見るんで
watch while predicting what you're saying.
大丈夫ですよ。いっぱいコメントしてね。
So please comment a lot!
あ、アッピピ？アッピピピ？アッピピ... お？
Ah, Appipi? Appipipi? Appipi... Oh?
何かを受信したみたいだ、これは... 悲報！
Looks like I've received a transmission... This is... Bad news!
…そうです。
...That's right.
YouTubeで放送している無料のチラ見せ、ここまでになっちゃうんだって。
The free preview on YouTube is apparently ending here.
コメント見えてんだけどさ、続きはね、SPWNで見られるらしいんだけど…
I can see the comments, but apparently you can watch the rest on SPWN...
見に来てくんないかなぁ…
Won't you come watch...?
見に来てくんない？ねぇ、みんなもお願いしてよ。
Won't you come watch? Come watch, okay? Hey, everyone, please ask them too.
見に来てくんないかなぁ…
Won't you come watch...?
わためぇともみんなもこう言ってますんで、
Watame-mates and everyone are saying this, so
あのね、初めて見たって人もね、ぜひ見てほしいなと思います。
even if it's your first time seeing me, I'd love for you to watch.
概要欄のね、リンクからぜひ遊びに来てください！
Please come visit via the link in the description!
え、それでは、わためは一旦ね、マイクを取りに行ってもいいですか？
Well then, may Watame go pick up the microphone for a moment?
いいよー！
Sure!
じゃあ一旦マイクをちょっと取りに行くので、みんなこの後も一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Alright, I'm going to go get the microphone, so let's keep the energy up together afterwards!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The free portion has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The free part has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!